hesgoal.com 2018-10-06

# Privacy Policy - HesGoal.COM Sports News

## Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy for www.hesgoal.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us using this form  **Contact US**   .

At www.hesgoal.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.hesgoal.com and how it is used.

**Disclaimer**

 We  **DO NOT**  host any videos on our web page. All videos found on our site are found freely available around the web. We make no guarantees or promises in our service and take no liability for our users actions. We are not affiliated nor claim to be affiliated with any of the owners of videos/streams played on our site. All content is copyright of their respective owners.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.hesgoal.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demograpballhic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.hesgoal.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.hesgoal.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.hesgoal.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.hesgoal.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.hesgoal.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.hesgoal.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**For The copyrights**

We do not host any files on our server and we don’t upload any Videos on other hosting websites.Our website works like a search engine, gathering and sorting Videos from other websites like ( Youtube, Dailymotion, etc ... ) and showing the embeded code or the direct link.Site owners hold no responsibility for any illegal usage of the content. If you have any legal issues please contact the appropriate media file owners / hosters, or report directly to us so we may remove the links to the streaming
